let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "This box looks dull.Paint it ________ red ________ green.(Conjuctions)",
    answer: "either...or",
    options: [
      "whereas",
      "because",
      "as well as",
      "either...or"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The cart eas selling ice cream __________ candies.(Conjuctions)",
    answer: "as well as",
    options: [
      "because",
      "as well as",
      "yet",
      "although"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "River Thames flows _________ London.(Preposition)",
    answer: "through",
    options: [
      "through",
      "on",
      "over",
      "at"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The children jumped __________ the pool.(Preposition)",
    answer: "into",
    options: [
      "on",
      "behing",
      "onto",
      "into"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "If you don't finish your lunch quickly, we ____________ be late.(Modal Auxillaries)",
    answer: "will",
    options: [
      "can",
      "would",
      "will",
      "must"
    ]
  },

 {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The president _________ visit our city, but I am not sure.(Modal Auxillaries)",
    answer: "might",
    options: [
      "must",
      "should",
      "might",
      "has to"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Somebody ______ talking outside the classroom.(Subject Verb Agreement)",
    answer: "is",
    options: [
      "are",
      "is",
      "has",
      "were"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Rhea and her grandmother ________ visiting us on Sunday.(Subject Verb Agreement)",
    answer: "are",
    options: [
      "has",
      "have",
      "are",
      "is"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Shreya(complete) ________ her homework by 8 p.m.(Tenses)",
    answer: "will complete",
    options: [
      "will complete",
      "has complete",
      "have complete",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Look! It ___________ (rain) again.(Tenses)",
    answer: "is raining",
    options: [
      "has raining",
      "is raining",
      "wil raining",
      "have been raining"
    ]
  },



];